after an insured person's admission to
hospital it also offers tele
consultations and recommendations for
routine health concerns by qualified
medical practitioner giving you more and
prompt access to Wellness
further on the ambulance cover feature
includes the expenses incurred on
emergency bases for using domestic air
ambulance services
the domestic air ambulance service
coverage is up to the sum insured
medical expenses incurred by in short
for daycare treatments as an inpatient
in a hospital for less than 24 hours are
also covered Home Care treatment expense
is also covered for a customer to opt to
get treated at the comfort of their
homes provided it is prescribed by the
doctor too apart from these enhanced
features the new Health Advantage plan
comes with a host of other benefits that
ensure robust coverage so give your
health care the advantage it deserves
with unci Lombard Health Advantage Apex
plus black